{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Interior Trim and Molding Installation Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40013/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40013,"taskName":"Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings - Install","taskDescription":"Install Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings","xmTaskDescriptor":"Interior Trim and Molding Installation Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4000,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenters Trim Decorative carpentry structural","textMessagingName":"Interior Trim/Mold","rolloverLongDesc":"Finish carpenters have special skills \u0026 tools that allow them to precisely cut \u0026 install molding \u0026 trim so that the joints are tight \u0026 nearly invisible.  Typically, their work remains visible \u0026 they therefore pay keen attention to the aesthetic details, as opposed to rough or frame carpenters who are largely unconcerned with aesthetics.","rolloverShortDesc":"Finish carpenters install trim \u0026 molding.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Crown Molding Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Interior Trim","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Interior Trim \u0026 Moldings Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Interior Trim Project","urlName":"Interior-Trim-and-Decorative-Moldings-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Crown Molding Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"trim, decorative, moulding, crown, cornice, baseboard, wainscoting, wainscoating, millwork, carpenter, carpentry, beadboard","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":337,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40013/":{"taskOID":40013,"originalTaskOID":40013,"setID":337,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":699,"questionDisplayText":"Features that Need Finish Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For the interior, which of the following features need finish work? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window casing","answerDisplayText":"Window casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2532,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor molding","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6747,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wall molding - paneling, wainscoting and chair rail","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding - paneling, wainscoting and chair rail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1297,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling molding - picture and crow","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding - picture and crow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1725,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6021,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stair system","answerDisplayText":"Stair system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2475,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Fireplace mantel","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace mantel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5636,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Laminate or wood countertops","answerDisplayText":"Laminate or wood countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5671,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms require finish or trim work?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":701,"questionDisplayText":"Doors \u0026 Windows to be Installed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following (doors and windows) do you need installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3320,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior doors","answerDisplayText":"Interior doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2318,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior doors","answerDisplayText":"Exterior doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":702,"questionDisplayText":"Need Finish Carpeter/Woodworker","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you looking for a finish carpenter/woodworker to complete multiple small projects?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":699,"questionDisplayText":"Features that Need Finish Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For the interior, which of the following features need finish work? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window casing","answerDisplayText":"Window casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2532,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor molding","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6747,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wall molding - paneling, wainscoting and chair rail","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding - paneling, wainscoting and chair rail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1297,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling molding - picture and crow","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding - picture and crow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1725,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6021,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stair system","answerDisplayText":"Stair system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2475,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Fireplace mantel","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace mantel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5636,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Laminate or wood countertops","answerDisplayText":"Laminate or wood countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window casing","answerDisplayText":"Window casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2532,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Floor molding","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6747,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wall molding - paneling, wainscoting and chair rail","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding - paneling, wainscoting and chair rail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1297,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ceiling molding - picture and crow","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding - picture and crow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1725,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6021,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stair system","answerDisplayText":"Stair system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2475,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Fireplace mantel","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace mantel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5636,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Laminate or wood countertops","answerDisplayText":"Laminate or wood countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5671,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms require finish or trim work?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":701,"questionDisplayText":"Doors \u0026 Windows to be Installed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following (doors and windows) do you need installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3320,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior doors","answerDisplayText":"Interior doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2318,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior doors","answerDisplayText":"Exterior doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3320,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior doors","answerDisplayText":"Interior doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2318,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior doors","answerDisplayText":"Exterior doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":702,"questionDisplayText":"Need Finish Carpeter/Woodworker","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you looking for a finish carpenter/woodworker to complete multiple small projects?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}